<airplane>
    <model>
        <modelname>Boeing747_300</modelname>
        <description> The Boeing 747-300 is an American wide-body commercial jet airliner and cargo aircraft, often referred
            to by its original nickname, Jumbo Jet. Its distinctive "hump" upper deck along the forward part of the aircraft
            makes it among the world's most recognizable aircraft,[6] and it was the first wide-body produced. </description>
    </model>
    <model>
        <modelname>Boeing747_400</modelname>
        <description> The Boeing 747-400 is an improvement of the 747-300, and is the best-selling model
            of the Boeing 747 family of jet airliners. While retaining the four-engine wide-body layout of its
            predecessors, the 747-400 embodies numerous technological and structural changes to produce a more efficient airframe.
            Its most distinguishing features versus preceding 747 models are 6-foot (1.8 m) winglets mounted on 6-foot (1.8 m) wing
            tip extensions,which are found on all 747-400s except for Japanese domestic market versions. </description>
    </model>
    <model>
        <modelname>Boeing747_8</modelname>
        <description> The Boeing 747-8 is a wide-body jet airliner developed by Boeing Commercial Airplanes. Officially announced
            in 2005, the 747-8 is the third generation of the 747, with a lengthened fuselage, redesigned wings, and improved efficiency.
            The 747-8 is the largest 747 version, the largest commercial aircraft built in the United States, and the longest passenger
            aircraft in the world.</description>
    </model>
    <model>
        <modelname>Airbus_A380_800</modelname>
        <description>The Airbus A380 is a double-deck, wide-body, four-engine jet airliner manufactured by European manufacturer Airbus.
            It is the world's largest passenger airliner, and the airports at which it operates have upgraded facilities to accommodate it.
            It was initially named Airbus A3XX and designed to challenge Boeing's monopoly in the large-aircraft market. The A380 made its
            first flight on 27 April 2005 and entered commercial service on 25 October 2007 with Singapore Airlines.</description>
    </model>
    <model>
        <modelname>Airbus_A320</modelname>
        <description>The Airbus A320 family consists of short- to medium-range, narrow-body, commercial passenger twin-engine jet airliners
            manufactured by Airbus. The family includes the A318, A319, A320 and A321, as well as the ACJ business jet. </description>
    </model>
    <model>
        <modelname>Airbus_A330_300</modelname>
        <description>The Airbus A330 is a medium- to long-range wide-body twin-engine jet airliner made by Airbus, a division of Airbus Group. </description>
    </model>
</airplane>